<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:id="@+id/main"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="@drawable/termsbg"
    tools:context=".ui.login.TermsConditions">

    <!-- ScrollView to make the content scrollable -->
    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:padding="16dp">

        <!-- TextView to display the terms and conditions -->
        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/terms_text"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:textColor="@android:color/black"
            android:textSize="16sp"
            android:lineSpacingExtra="4dp"
            android:text="TERMS OF SERVICE AGREEMENT
            \n\nPlease read the following terms of service agreement carefully. By accessing or using our sites and our services, you hereby agree to be bound by the terms and all terms incorporated herein by reference. It is the responsibility of you, the user, customer, or prospective customer to read the terms and conditions before proceeding to use this site. If you do not expressly agree to all of the terms and conditions, then please do not access or use our sites or our services. This terms of service agreement is effective as of 08/15/2017.
            \n\nACCEPTANCE OF TERMS
            \n\nThe following terms of service agreement (the 'TOS') is a legally binding agreement that shall govern the relationship with our users and others which may interact or interface with TELENETDOCTOR™, including ETS platform, LLC, located at 300 Sevilla avenue S310, coral gables, Florida 33134 and its subsidiaries, associates, providers and affiliates hereinafter referred to as ETSP, in association with the use of the TELENETDOCTOR™ site, (the 'Site') and services as provided by ETSP, which shall be defined below.
            \n\nDESCRIPTION OF WEBSITE SERVICES OFFERED
            \n\nThe site provides information and services related to telemedicine and patient monitoring and wellness. Any and all visitors to our site shall be deemed as 'Users' of the herein contained services provided for the purpose of this TOS.
            \n\nThe user acknowledges and agrees that the services provided and made available through our website and applications, which may include some mobile applications, are the sole property of ETSP. At its discretion, ETSP may offer additional website services and/or products, or update, modify or revise any current content and services, and this agreement shall apply to any and all additional services and/or products and any and all updated, modified or revised services unless otherwise stipulated. ETSP does hereby reserve the right to cancel and cease offering any of the aforementioned services and/or products. You, as the end user acknowledge, accept, and agree that ETSP shall not be held liable for any such updates, modifications, revisions, suspensions or discontinuance of any of our services and/or products. Your continued use of the services provided, after such posting of any updates, changes, and/or modifications shall constitute your acceptance of such updates, changes and/or modifications, and as such, frequent review of this agreement and any and all applicable terms and policies should be made by you to ensure you are aware of all terms and policies currently in effect. Should you not agree to the updated, revised, or.
            \n\nFurthermore, the user understands, acknowledges and agrees that the services offered shall be provided 'As is' and as such ETSP shall not assume any responsibility or obligation for the timeliness, missed delivery, deletion, and/or any failure to store user content, communication or personalization settings."
            android:layout_marginBottom="16dp"/>
    </ScrollView>

</RelativeLayout>
